now coming to the stage her first roast
appearance
was actually at a witch burning she's
old is what i'm saying it's just a joke
it's the golden girl with the platinum
jokes
betty white you know
i've been a huge trekkie ever since the
show first aired and that's why i'm so
thrilled to see michelle and george
takei here tonight
because let's face it we all know
shatner's nuts but
george has actually tasted them
[Applause]
i like the sweet grandma and dirty humor
this is
gr he's melting this this homosexual is
losing his mind
this is called a gay gasm you may not
know this when you're queer and you see
a woman you love on stage you're
transformed
to a new level of happiness damn it's so
amazing to see like a 99 year old lady
really go there it's kind of like when
you go to the buffet in south florida
and they're sticking the chicken wings
in their purse they just don't care
man good for betty's with the little old
lady delivery grandma
bacon cookies got a worthless
original in her pocket but she can still
zenya when she needs to oh
it always makes me laugh when i see
artie lang on stage
knowing i'm going to outlive him
no no no no
that's the sad thing we all know betty
white's alive
we're like is are you like
i love already lying i don't want him to
to die but
i mean if you look at a picture of betty
white and the picture already lagging
it's starting to
overlap a little they look the same you
know at the time of taping they're both
still alive and it's really anybody's
game
i mean who doesn't love betty white just
yeah one of my favorites just went up
there and gave everyone an
that's what she did
roasts aren't just a good time they also
promote global harmony
i mean where else could you find a
supermodel from germany and a comedian
from boston
joining forces to make fun of jeff
boxworthy
well there's actually no need to
visualize world peace because it is
right here
at moment 59 patrice o'neill supermodel
translator
hello jeff yesterday
um
wow girl go into like the dressing room
of whatever victoria secrets you're in
because i can't focus when there is like
lingerie hanging behind you with no
explanation for that you're in the mall
right now when this thing comes hey it's
me
heidi yo jeff what's up
check it out i'm chilling in germany
right now but i wanted to give you your
props on comedy central
yeah um i said hell jeff's my dog and
that mullet-headed fool is straight up
funny that's so funny
oh it's always so good to see patrice yo
jeff remember the time we was cold
lamping at the
club and she said co-labor i think she
did
and you was like yo want to hear a joke
and i was like
i was gonna shine and then you busted
out all that redneck flavor
man you got us white people down cool i
knew patrice so
i could totally see heidi klum kicking
it with patrice o'neill of course yes
swag
you know and heidi klum's hot so why not
i think they would have chilled for sure
more so than i think she would have
chilled with jeff
[Laughter]
when you talk about the mount rushmore
of comedians patrice holds
more than one spot up there he's one of
the best in the moment just adeliben
he was great i mean rest in peace
patrice o'neill
peace out west side
[Applause]
you